Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Clipping file, ca. 1920-1980
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan
  - F
    - Foreign Students-Scholarships and Exchange. (Box 28)
      (Includes scholarships and fellowships to foreign students, exchange student plans, and undergraduate study abroad for MiU student see also: Student Government (exchange with Free University of Berlin); Law School (Japanese-American program for cooperation in Legal Studies); Foreign Visitors)
    - Foreign Students-Societies-Africa and the Near East (Box 28)
    - Foreign Students-Societies-Asia (Box 28)
    - Foreign Students-Societies-Cosmopolitan Club (Box 28)
    - Foreign Students-Societies-Europe (Box 28)
    - Foreign Students-Societies-South America and Philippines (Box 28)
    - Foreign Study
      - Undergraduate
        (see: Foreign Students-Scholarships and Exchange; Literary College (for its foreign study program))
      - Graduate
      - Faculty
    - Foreign Visitors.
      (See also: Foreign Students; Institute of Social Research-Survey Research Center; Foreign Students-International Center; Linguistic Institute; Summer Session-Campus Events (for the summer lecture series); Latin-American Relations See also: departments sponsoring.)
      - 1920-August 1932 (Box 28)
      - September 1932-1941 (Box 28)
      - 1942-1951 (Box 28)
      - 1952-1956 (Box 28)
      - 1957- (Box 28)
    - Foreman's Conference.
      (see: Extension-Foreman's Conference)
    - Forestry.
      (1903-1926 Dept. of Forestry; 1927-1929 School of Forestry; 1950-see: Natural Resources, School of)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 28)
      - 1930-1937 (Box 28)
      - 1938-1944 (Box 28)
      - 1945-1950 (Box 28)
    - Forestry Club.
      (see: Forestry (1903-49); Natural Resources, School of (1950-))
    - Fortnight.
    - Forums. General and Miscellaneous (Box 28)
      (See also: Michigan Forum (Student Government sponsor); Union-Forums; Foreign Students-International Center; Political Clubs (and individual clubs); Foreign Students-International Students Association.; Radicals; Student Town Hall)
    - Foundation for Research on Human Behavior. (Box 28)
      (An independent group using university facilities. Prof. Hayes, Economics Dept. chairman (1957))
    - Franklin Statue.
    - Fraternities (Professional).
      (see: Professional fraternities)
    - Fraternities (Social)
      (See also: Fraternities-(alphabetical); Discipline;-Fraternity Buying Association (FBA); Greek Week; Hectorians; Housing; Interfraternity Ball; Interfraternity Council (IFC); Interfraternity Sing;-Rushing; Crime; Sororities-Panhellenic (joint activities); Race problems (bias clause); Prohibition;)
      - General
        - 1920-1934 (Box 28)
        - 1934-1949 (Box 28)
        - 1950- (Box 28)
    - Fraternities (alphabetical):
      (For materials on individual fraternities see also: Fraternities-Rushing; Discipline; Housing; Crime; Fraternities; Prohibition; Race Problems)
      - Acacia (Box 28)
      - Alpha Tau Omega (Box 28)
      - A (Box 28)
      - C (Box 28)
      - D-E (Box 28)
      - F-K (Box 28)
      - L-0 (Box 28)
      - P-Q (Box 28)
      - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 28)
      - Phi Kappa Sigma (Box 28)
      - R-S (Box 28)
      - Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 28)
      - T-Z (Box 28)
    - Fraternities-Interfraternity Sing
    - Fraternities-Alumni Relations.
      (See: Fraternities (general, Interfraternity Alumni Conference 1932 Stewart Howe Alumni Service, scholarship (earlier years), etc.); Fraternities Interfraternity Council (scholarship, meetings, etc.))
    - Fraternities.-Bias Clause.
      (see: Race Problems. For individual fraternities, see: Fraternities-(Alphabetical))
    - Fraternities-Charities.
      (see: Fraternities (older years only);)
    - Fraternities-Interfraternity Council Fraternities-Rushing (Help Week, etc
    - Fraternities-Christmas Party.
      (see: Fraternities-Interfraternity Council)
    - Fraternities-Discipline. (Box 28)
      (Includes Interfraternity Councils Executive Council (also called Judiciary Council). Includes social infractions. For other types see also: Rushing infractions; Fraternities-Rushing ;Financial difficulties; Fraternities-and Fraternities-Interfraternity Council-Drinking Violations; Prohibition Closed dance question; Fraternities-Interfraternity Council. Cases appealed to Joint Judie.-Student Government-Joint Judiciary Council.)
    - Fraternities-Fraternity Buying Association (FBA) Fraternities-Fraternity-Faculty Forums. (Box 28)
      (see: Fraternities)
    - Fraternities-Greek Week. (Box 28)
      (Includes Interfraternity Council and Panhellenic workshops, Olympiad Night, etc. see also: Fraternities-Interfraternity Sing; Fraternities-Interfraternity Ball)
    - Fraternities-Health and Safety Programs.
      (see: Fraternities-Housing)
    - Fraternities-Hectorians. Fraternity Honorary (Box 28)
    - Fraternities-Housing.
      (Includes question of freshmen residence, 2.4 grade controversy, building program, fire prevention, health and safety plans, taxation of property, etc. For food see: Fraternities"-Fraternity Buying Association)
      - 1925-1955 (Box 28)
      - 1956- (Box 28)
    - Fraternities-Interfraternity Ball (Box 28)
    - Fraternities-Interfraternity Council.
      (Includes Talent Show, Christmas Party, closed dance controversy, Fraternity Presidents Association, National Interfraternity Council, financial questions, scholarship, etc.; For sponsored association (Jr. Interfraternity Council, IFC Pledge Banquet) see Fraternities-Rushing.)
      - 1920-1938 (Box 29)
      - 1939-1953 (Box 29)
      - 1954- (Box 29)
    - Fraternities-Interfraternity Sing (Box 29)
    - Fraternities-Rushing.
      (see also: Fraternities-Housing)
      - 1920-1935 (Box 29)
      - 1935-1945 (Box 29)
      - 1946-1952 (Box 29)
      - 1953-1955 (Box 29)
      - 1956- (Box 29)
    - Fraternities-Taxation.
    - Fraternity Buying Association
      (see: Fraternities-Fraternity Buying Association)
    - Fraternity Initiation Banquet (Union) 1935-.
      (See: Fraternities-Rushing)
    - Fraternity Representatives Assembly.
      (see: Fraternities-Inter-fraternity Council)
    - "Free University of Ann Arbor" (1966).
      (see: Curriculum Established by "Activist" faculty and students dissatisfied with MiU and its course offerings.)
    - Free Speech.
      (see also: (for speaker's ban decisions): Academic Freedom; Oratorical Series; Political Clubs -- Democratic, Progressives,-Mich. Youth for Democratic Action;-Civil Liberties Committee; Censorship; Alumni-Miller, Arthur; Radicals)
      - January-October 1952 (Box 29)
      - October 1952- (Box 29)
    - Free University of Berlin Exchange Scholarships.
      (see: Student Government (1957-))
    - Freer Manuscripts.
      (see: Gifts)
    - French Club.
    - French Language and Literature.
      (see: Romance Lang. and Lit., Dept. of)
    - Fresh Air Camp.
      (see also: Institute for Human Adjustment (of which it is a part-T; Fraternities-Rushing (work donated); Sororities-Rushing (work donated); (departments offering credit for work at the camp)-Education, Sociology, Social Work; Psychology, Physical Education)
      - 1926-1937 (Box 29)
      - 1938-1947 (Box 29)
      - 1948-1953 (Box 29)
      - 1954 (Box 29)
    - Freshman.
      (Includes Freshman orientation, Freshman Night and Banquet, Principal-Freshman Conference. see also: Freshman-Frosh Weekend; Freshman -- Caps; Games, Freshman-Sophomore; Traditions; Lantern Night (for pageant and project) Advisors; Student Religious Association. (for roundtable); Annual official publication titled Information for Prospective Freshmen. Administrative Studies. V.1 No. 1, 1927)
      - 1920-February 1932 (Box 29)
      - March 1932-1937 (Box 29)
      - 1938-1946 (Box 29)
      - 1947-1950 (Box 29)
      - 1951-1954 (Box 29)
      - 1955- (Box 29)
    - Freshmen-Caps (1906-34). (Box 29)
      (see also: Student Council)
    - Freshmen-Frosh Weekend. Also called Freshmen Frolic, Student Legislature Tug Week, etc. (Box 29)
      (see also: Games. Freshmen-Sophomore)
    - Freshmen Frolic.
      (see: Freshmen-Frosh Weekend)
    - Freshman Rendezvous.
      (see: Student Religious Organization (1957-); Student Religious Association (1937-1956))
    - Frieze Memorial Organ.
      (see: Organ)
    - Frosh Weekend.
    - Fulbright Fellowships.
      (see: Fellowships; Foreign Students-Scholarships and Exchanges)
    - Future Teachers of America
  - G
    - Galens.
    - Games. Freshmen-Sophomore
      - 1920-1931 (Box 29)
      - 1932-1945 (Box 29)
    - Gamma Alpha.
      (see: Societies-Science)
    - Gamma Delta.
      (see: Religion-Churches-Lutheran)
    - "Gamson Pledge" (1966-).
      (see: Student Records. "Concerning formal letter grades for male undergraduates subject to the draft.")
    - Gargoyle.
      (Includes also Mongrel, Wrinkle. See also: Student Publications (for general info))
      - 1920-1952 (Box 29)
      - 1953- (Box 29)
    - Gay Liberation Front.
      (see: Homosexuality (general file))
    - Gems.
      (see: Mineralogy, Dept. of)
    - Generation.
    - Geography, Dept. of. (Box 29)
      (Includes Geography Camps at Seney and Shingleton, Mich. (U.P.)-Camp Cusino.)
    - Geology, Dept. of.
      (see also: Mineralogy, Dept. of; Engineering, College of -- Camp Davis; Societies-Science (for Geology-Mineralogy Journal Club); Camp Davis, Wyoming is used for surveying field work. Geology Field Station at State Bridge, Colorado is used for geology field work.)
      - 1921-1952 (Box 29)
      - 1953- (Box 29)
    - Geology Field Station (State Bridge, Colorado).
    - Geology-Mineralogy Journal Club.
    - George (Edwin S.) Reserve.
      (see: Museums (Is under the Museum of Zoology))
    - German Club (a radio broadcast).
      (see: Radio-WUOM)
    - German Research Club.
    - German Table. Faculty group.
    - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Dept. of
    - Gerontology, Division. of.
      (see: Institute for Human Adjustment-Gerontology, Division of)
    - Gifts.
      (see also: names of individuals (e.g. Cook, W.W.) and recipients (e.g. Burton Tower; Graduate School; Library-Gifts) Finances-Alumni Aid; Finances-$55 Million Program)
      - 1922-1928 (Box 30)
      - 1928-1937 (Box 30)
      - 1938-1948 (Box 30)
      - 1948-1953 (Box 30)
      - 1954- (Box 30)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan Society
    - Girl's Glee Club
      (Former title of the Women's Glee Club)
    - Glacial Geology and Polar Research Laboratory (Estab. 1961)
    - Glee Clubs.
      (Includes Men's Glee Club, Women's Glee Club, Extension Choir, Novelaires, etc. Also joint concerts with other university glee clubs. Includes former groups-Varsity Men's Glee Club, Girl's Glee Club, Stanley Chorus, Soldier Choir. see also: Glee Clubs-University Choir; Glee Clubs-Extra .cu curricular; Glee Clubs-Misc.; Glee Clubs-Gulantics; Music Series)
    - Glee Clubs-Extra Curricular Groups. (Box 30)
      (Includes the Arts Chorale (Literary College group), Michigan Singers (small group of advanced singers))
    - Glee Clubs-Gulantics Disc., 1957 (Box 30)
    - Glee Clubs-Misc. (Box 30)
      (Includes campus vocal groups not sponsored by the School of Music, Ann Arbor Community Sing, Bach concerts by high school students under the School of Music, and other misc. groups. see also: Fraternities-IFC (for IFC Sing))
    - Glee Clubs-University Choir. (Box 30)
      (Contains three sections: Women's Choir, Men's Choir, and a mixed training choir. Includes Bach Choir and adds other groups under its title for Christmas concerts.)
    - Glider Club.
    - Golden Rule Ball.
    - Golf. (Box 30)
      (Includes golf field and club house)
    - Golf-Women (Box 30)
    - (Moses and Sophia) Gomberg Chemistry Awards.
      (see: Fellowships; Scholarships; Prizes)
    - Gothic Film. Society.
      (see: Moving Pictures-Gothic Film Society)
    - Grace Bible Church Student Guild.
    - Grades.
    - Graduate Education Club.
      (see: Societies -- Education)
    - Graduate Employee Organization. (Box 30)
    - Graduate Outing Club.
      (see:,Societies-Outing)
    - Graduate School (Horace Rackham).
      (Includes Graduate School Council. For various graduate clubs, see the dept. concerned or Societies. see also: Graduate School-Exhibits in Bldg.; Graduate School-State Teachers: Colleges)
      - 1923-1937 (Box 30)
      - 1938-1940 (Box 30)
      - 1940-1953 (Box 30)
    - Graduate Round Table.
      (A series sponsored by the Political Science Dept. see: Political Science, Dept. of)
    - Graduate School-Exhibits in Building.
      (Includes (Mich.) Amateur Art Exhibit. Michigan Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters Exhibits)
      - 1939-1952 (Box 30)
      - 1953- (Box 30)
    - Graduate School (Horace H. Rackham)-State Teachers Colleges Graduate Women's Club. (Box 30)
      (see: Societies-Women)
    - Great Books Courses.
      (see: Curriculum)
    - Great Lakes Research.
      (Includes Great Lakes Research Institute; Great Lakes Commission; (International) Great Lakes Fishery Commission; Fisheries Investigation and Fisheries 4ureau of the U.S. Fish and Wild 'Life Service. In 196G Great Lakes Research became a division of the Institute of Science and Technology. See also: Engineering, College of-Marine and Mechanical (for Lake Hydraulic Lab., Naval Engineering, etc.); Museums; Water Pollution Research)
    - Greek Language and Literature.
    - Greek Orthodox (Eastern Orthodox Student Society)
    - "Greek Week".
      (see: Fraternities-Greek Week)
    - Green Feather Campaign (McCarthy).
      (see: Political Clubs-Democrats)
    - Greenland Expedition.
      (see: Expeditions-Greenland)
    - Gridgraph.
      (see: Football-Gridgraph)
    - Gridiron Knights Banquet.
      (see: Sigma Delta Chi)
    - GROUP (Government Revision of University Policy. 1965-)
      (see: Political Clubs; Elections)
    - Group Dynamics.
      (see: institute for Social Research-Research Center for Group Dynamics)
    - Guide Services and Tours.
    - Guild House (Ecumenical).
    - Gulantics.
      (All-campus talent show sponsored by the Glee Clubs, Union, and League. Disc. 1957. see Glee Clubs-Gulantics)
    - Gym-Jam.
      (see: Athletics -- WAA)
    - Gymnastics (Box 30)
  - H
    - Hall of Biological Principles.
    - Hall of Evolution.
    - Hampstead Community Players. Faculty, students, and townspeople group to produce medieval and Shakespearean amateur plays.
    - Handball.
      (see: Athletics-Intramural)
    - Agatha Harrison International House (women).
      (see: Foreign Students-Housing)
    - Harvard Club.
      (see: Societies-G-P)
    - Hatcher, Harlan H.
      - 1951 (Box 30)
      - 1952 (Box 30)
      - 1954-1954 (Box 30)
      - 1955-1959 (Box 30)
      - 1960- (Box 30)
    - Hatcher Commission Report on Student Decision Making.
    - Haven, Erastus (Pres.)
    - Haven Hall. (Box 31)
      (see also: Angell Hall; Building Program)
    - Hawaii Club.
    - Hayden Memorial Library.
      (see: Faculty-Hayden, J.R.-Hayden Memorial)
    - Hazing.
      (see: Fraternities-Rushing; Sororities-Rushing; Societies-Honor; Freshman; Traditions;)
    - Health Service.
      (see also; Hospitalization Plans; Student Accidents Hearing Center. see: Medical School-Research)
      - 1920-1933 (Box 31)
      - 1934-1936 (Box 31)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 31)
      - 1940-1946 (Box 31)
      - 1947-1953 (Box 31)
      - 1954- (Box 31)
    - Heating and Power Plant.
      (see: Buildings and Grounds)
    - Hectorians.
      (see: Fraternities-Hectorians)
    - Hell Week.
      (see: Fraternities-Rushing)
    - Hellenic Association.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Europe Help Week. see: Fraternities-Rushing)
    - Henderson House.
    - Herbarium and Krieger Mycological Library.
      (see: Museums; Botany, Dept. of)
    - Heredity (Human). Institute of Human Biology est. 1940. (Box 31)
      (Included Laboratory of Vertebrate Biology, Heredity Clinic (a public service). Dissolved July 1, 1956. Inst. of Human Biology and Heredity Clinic became Dept. of Genetics in the School of Medicine. (See: Medical School* Lab of Vertebrate Biology transferred to Dept. of Zoology. See Zoology, Dept. of; Buhl Ugaer under Medical School)
    - Heredity Clinic.
      (See: Heredity (Human))
    - Hi Fi Club.
    - Hiawatha Club (Students from the Upper Penn.).
      (see: Societies G-P)
    - High Altitude Engineering Laboratory.
      (see: Space Research)
    - High school inspection.
      (see: Bureau of School Services; High Schools, Accredited (general file))
    - Higher Education.
    - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 31)
    - Hildebrand (W.0.) Fund.
      (see: Business Administration, School of (for insurance education))
    - Hill Auditorium. see also: Free Speech; Organ; Stearns Musical Collection (Box 31)
    - Hillel Players.
    - Hillelzapoppin.
    - Hindustan Students Association became split into Indian Stud. Association and Pakistan Club
    - History
      (see also: History-Foundation of the University; History-Pictures; History-Michigan Historical Collections; History-Centennial (1937); History-Centennial-College of Lit., Science and Arts (1941))
      - I (Period (1817-1900) (Box 31)
      - II (Period 1900-1946) (Box 31)
    - History-Centennial (1937) (Box 31)
    - History-Centennial (College of Literature, Science and Arts, 1941) (Box 31)
    - History. "First Facts" (Box 31)
    - History-Foundation of the University (Box 31)
    - History-Michigan Historical Collections.
      - 1936-1949 (Box 31)
      - 1950- (Box 31)
    - History-Pictures (Box 31)
    - History-Sesquicentennial. (Box 31)
      (see also: Finances-55 Million Program)
    - History, Dept. or (Box 31)
    - History of Art Dept.
    - Hockey and Skating
      - 1920-1956 (Box 31)
      - 1957- (Box 31)
    - Holden Perinatal Research Laboratory (Box 31)
    - Home and Home Games.
    - Homecoming.
      (see: Alumni-Homecoming)
    - Home-School Community Relationships.
      (Workshops sponsored by School of Education and Michigan Congress of Parents and Teachers. see: Education, School of-Workshops)
    - Honor Societies.
      (see: Societies-Honor)
    - Honor Systems.
      (Includes question of unproctored exams. see also: Engineering, College of-Engineering Council)
      - 1920-1956 (Box 31)
      - 1957- (Box 31)
    - Honors Convocations--Programs
      - 1920-1954 (Box 31)
      - 1955-
    - Honors Council Plan. Plan in the Literary College, 1956-/3-(12
      (see: Honors Program)
    - Honors Housing.
      (see: Dormitories-General)
    - Honors Program.
      (see also: Honors Convocations)
      - 1920-1956 (Box 32)
      - 1957 (Box 32)
    - Hopwood Award -- Clippings
      (for Hopwood see also: Dictionary of American Biography)
      - 1930-1933 (Box 32)
      - 1934-1936 (Box 32)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 32)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 32)
      - 1943-1946 (Box 32)
      - 1947-1949 (Box 32)
      - 1950-1953 (Box 32)
      - 1954- (Box 32)
    - Horner's Woods.
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of.
    - Hospital and medical economics report.
    - Hospital Management Studies.
    - Hospitalization Plans (Box 32)
      (Includes staff, student, and studies done for the Michigan legislature.)
    - Hospitals. Medical Center
      (includes: University Hospital 1925; 'Women's hospital 1950 Outpatient Clinic; Contagious Hospital Children's Hospital see also: Medical School; Nurses; Simpson Memorial; Kresge Medical; Veteran's Readjustment; Psychiatry; Pharmacy, College of; Societies-Galens; Christmas Events.)
      - 1920-1930, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - 1931-1937 (Box 32)
      - 1937-1940 (Box 32)
      - 1941-1945 (Box 32)
      - 1946-1948 (Box 32)
      - 1949-1951 (Box 32)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 32)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 32)
      - 1956-1962 (Box 32)
      - 1963-1966 (Box 32)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 32)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 32)
      - 1973- (Box 32)
    - Hospitals-Clinical Research Unit.
    - Hospitals-Social Services.
      (Includes hospital school. Hospitals-Volunteer Services. see: Hospitals. (Includes: Student Volunteer Services (MTUT; Soph Project (Mill); Hospital Volunteer Services (AA) see also: Individual groups-e.g. Societies-Galens; Fraternities-; Sororities-; Christmas Events)
      - 1920-1949 (Box 32)
      - 1950- (Box 32)
    - Hosteling Club.
      (see: Societies-Outing)
    - Hours, Late.
      (see: Women's Judiciary Council (rules and infraction-Calendar (as part of the gen. scheduling question); Dean-Women; Dormitories-Women (in individual dorms); Student Affairs, Office of 1962-)
    - Housing.
      (see also: Housing-Women; Dorms-Men; Dorms-Women; Cooperative Rooming and Boarding Projects; Food Service Bldg.; Race Problems (for discrimination); Institute for Social Research-Survey Research Center (for surveys of AA))
      - 1920-1938 (Box 32)
      - 1939-1945 (Box 32)
      - 1946 (Box 32)
      - 1947 (Box 32)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 32)
      - 1951-1953 (Box 32)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 32)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 33)
      - 1958-1965 (Box 33)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 33)
      - 1969 (Box 33)
      - 1970 (Box 33)
    - Housing women. Dorms-women; cooperative Boarding and Rooming Projects (Box 33)
    - Huber Committee.
      (see: Michigan-Politicians-H-Q)
    - Human Behavior.
      (see: Workshop in Human Behavior see: Education, School of-Workshops; Foundation for Research in Human Behavior)
    - Human Genetics, Dept. of.
      (see: Medical School-Research. Before July 1956 known as the Institute of Human Biology. See: Heredity (Human))
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for.
      (see: Center for Human Growth and Development.)
    - Human Performance Center.
    - Human Relations Board 1954-.
    - Human Relations Coordinator 1968-
    - (American) Humanist Association.
      (see: Religion-Churches Unitarian)
    - Hungarian Uprising, 1956
      (see: Foreign Students-Displaced Persons.)
    - Hutchins, President Harry B. (Box 33)
    - Hutchins Hall. Law classrooms.
    - Hyde Park.
      (see: Campus Opinion)
  - I
    - IFC.
    - I.H.C. (Interhouse Council).
      (see: Dorms (Men)-IHC)
    - I Hop. Joint project of Assembly and AIM or IHC.
      (see: Independents)
    - IRCE (Institutional Research Council of Eleven).
    - Identification cards.
      (see: Registration and classification.)
    - Il Circolo Italiano.
      (see: Societies-Il Circolo Italiano)
    - Independent Men's Association.
      (see: Congress)
    - Independents. (Box 33)
      (For joint actions of women and men's organizations only. see also: Assembly; Dorms (Men)-Inter-House Council. For earlier organizations see cards labeled Independents(Men) and Independents (Women).)
    - Independents (Men)
      (see: Congress (1937-44); Association for Independent Men (AIM); (1948-52); Dorms (Men)-Inter-house Council (1952-); Independents (joint action with Assembly) Societies-Independents; Societies-Quadrants)
    - Independents (Women)
      (see: Assembly; Independents (joint action); Societies-Independent; Societies-Women; Societies-Senior Society)
    - Indian Students Association.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Asia Indian (Amer.) Archaeology. see: Anthropology, Dept. of)
    - Industrial Development Davison. See Institute of Technology
    - Industrial Health, Dept. of.
      (see: Public Health; School-of)
    - Industrial Relations, Bureau.
    - Industrial Relations Club.
    - Industrial Sciences Group (Part of Cooley Electronics Lab.)
      (see: Engineering, College of-North Campus; Infantry Officers Club. see: R.O.T.C.)
    - Information and News Services.
    - Infrared Information and Analysis Center (Willow Run) (IRIA
      (see: Engineering, College of-Engineering Research Institute, November 1964-see Institute of Sci. and Tech.)
    - Inland Review.